{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649460867","data":{"timestamp":" 947649460867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" 294c7c40-be17-4e38-a100-629701f838bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_6-9-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649467645","data":{"timestamp":" 947649467645"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" 294c7c40-be17-4e38-a100-629701f838bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-7-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649469722","data":{"timestamp":" 947649469722"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" 294c7c40-be17-4e38-a100-629701f838bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-7-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649480504","data":{"timestamp":" 947649480504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" bbc5cff9-f5c6-435f-8549-f811254968c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649480728","data":{"timestamp":" 947649480728"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" bbc5cff9-f5c6-435f-8549-f811254968c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649481691","data":{"timestamp":" 947649481691"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" bbc5cff9-f5c6-435f-8549-f811254968c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649482964","data":{"timestamp":" 947649482964"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" bbc5cff9-f5c6-435f-8549-f811254968c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649485799","data":{"timestamp":" 947649485799"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" bbc5cff9-f5c6-435f-8549-f811254968c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649486649","data":{"timestamp":" 947649486649"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" bbc5cff9-f5c6-435f-8549-f811254968c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649486970","data":{"timestamp":" 947649486970"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" bbc5cff9-f5c6-435f-8549-f811254968c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649488202","data":{"timestamp":" 947649488202"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" bbc5cff9-f5c6-435f-8549-f811254968c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649491677","data":{"timestamp":" 947649491676"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" bbc5cff9-f5c6-435f-8549-f811254968c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649492666","data":{"timestamp":" 947649492666"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" bbc5cff9-f5c6-435f-8549-f811254968c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649492924","data":{"timestamp":" 947649492924"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" bbc5cff9-f5c6-435f-8549-f811254968c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649493885","data":{"timestamp":" 947649493885"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" bbc5cff9-f5c6-435f-8549-f811254968c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649496805","data":{"timestamp":" 947649496804"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" bbc5cff9-f5c6-435f-8549-f811254968c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649497837","data":{"timestamp":" 947649497837"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" bbc5cff9-f5c6-435f-8549-f811254968c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649498309","data":{"timestamp":" 947649498309"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" bbc5cff9-f5c6-435f-8549-f811254968c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649502895","data":{"timestamp":" 947649502894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" bbc5cff9-f5c6-435f-8549-f811254968c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649503008","data":{"timestamp":" 947649503008"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" bbc5cff9-f5c6-435f-8549-f811254968c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.cap.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649520427","data":{"timestamp":" 947649520427"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" 3bf54b67-f844-4f89-a56d-b25ce23c80c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.cap.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.cap.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649529818","data":{"timestamp":" 947649529817"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" 3bf54b67-f844-4f89-a56d-b25ce23c80c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.cap.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.cap.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649538967","data":{"timestamp":" 947649538967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" 3bf54b67-f844-4f89-a56d-b25ce23c80c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.cap.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.cap.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649539056","data":{"timestamp":" 947649539056"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" 3bf54b67-f844-4f89-a56d-b25ce23c80c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.cap.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.cap.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649549567","data":{"timestamp":" 947649549567"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" 3bf54b67-f844-4f89-a56d-b25ce23c80c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.cap.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.cap.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649557144","data":{"timestamp":" 947649557144"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" 3bf54b67-f844-4f89-a56d-b25ce23c80c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.cap.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.cap.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649562457","data":{"timestamp":" 947649562457"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" 3bf54b67-f844-4f89-a56d-b25ce23c80c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.cap.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.cap.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649568850","data":{"timestamp":" 947649568849"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" 3bf54b67-f844-4f89-a56d-b25ce23c80c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.cap.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.cap.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649578271","data":{"timestamp":" 947649578271"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" 3bf54b67-f844-4f89-a56d-b25ce23c80c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.cap.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.cap.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649581123","data":{"timestamp":" 947649581123"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" 3bf54b67-f844-4f89-a56d-b25ce23c80c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.cap.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.cap.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649582080","data":{"timestamp":" 947649582080"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" 3bf54b67-f844-4f89-a56d-b25ce23c80c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.cap.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.cap.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649587185","data":{"timestamp":" 947649587185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" 3bf54b67-f844-4f89-a56d-b25ce23c80c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.cap.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.cap.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649588818","data":{"timestamp":" 947649588817"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" 3bf54b67-f844-4f89-a56d-b25ce23c80c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.cap.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.cap.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649594431","data":{"timestamp":" 947649594431"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" 3bf54b67-f844-4f89-a56d-b25ce23c80c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.cap.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.cap.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649602293","data":{"timestamp":" 947649602292"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" 3bf54b67-f844-4f89-a56d-b25ce23c80c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.cap.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.cap.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649621941","data":{"timestamp":" 947649621940"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" 3bf54b67-f844-4f89-a56d-b25ce23c80c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.cap.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.cap.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649637710","data":{"timestamp":" 947649637709"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" 004e53c9-a282-4301-8bdd-bf4ed36cfef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.cap.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.cap.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649654206","data":{"timestamp":" 947649654206"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" 004e53c9-a282-4301-8bdd-bf4ed36cfef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.cap.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649694928","data":{"timestamp":" 947649694928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_065718"," gameId":" 004e53c9-a282-4301-8bdd-bf4ed36cfef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.cap.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}